

export const questionsList = [
    {question:"Dep. Name",
    answers:['740K Assembly L4 & L5', '740K Filter Welding AT', 'A&B Assembly', 'AC Panel', 'ARM Anodizing', 'ARM Assembly', 'ARM Packaging', 'ARM Paint', 'ARM Press', 'ARM Washing', 'AT Inspection, Filter Welding & Washers', 'AT Machining', 'AT Machining 740K', 'AT Measurements', 'AT Solenoid', 'Accounting', 'Accounting (IPP)', 'Accounting (SPP)', 'Am Sales D.F.', 'Assembly Maintenance (CPS)', 'Assembly Maintenance (EGC, MTS, WSS, APP)', 'Assy Maintenance (GPP)', 'Audit', 'BP Elastomer Molding', 'BP HVAC Molding I-181', 'BP HVAC Molding I-182', 'BP HVAC Molding L1 / L3 / L6', 'BP HVAC Molding L2 / L4', 'CCV', 'CID', 'CRFM L2', 'Continuous Improvement', 'Coolant Control (For Machining)', 'Corporate Executive', 'Corporate Strategy Planning', 'DIAM Design Center Cost', 'DIAM Quality Eng', 'DMMI Lab Center Cost', 'DNA', 'DNA (SPP)', 'DNA Direct (SPP)', 'DNMX Legal', 'DPAM Warehouse', 'Die Cast AT Solenoid', 'Die Cast Dies Maintenance (EGC, MTS, APP)', 'Die Cast Machines Maintenance (EGC, MTS, APP)', 'Die Cast OCV', 'Die Cast VCT', 'Die Shop Common', 'Dies Maintenance (GPP)', 'Direct (EC)', 'Direct (M&L)', 'ECF L2', 'ECM Crfm ', 'ECM L1', 'ECM L2', 'ECM L3', 'ECM Molding P-tanks 1', 'ECM Molding P-tanks 2', 'ECM Molding SHD & Fan', 'ECM Molding SHD1300T', 'EGC Parts MC', 'ELCM 2.0 Assy', 'ELCM 2.5 Assy', 'ELCM 2.5 Molding', 'ELCM Molding', 'Evap Front Process', 'Evap NBF / Hellium Leak', 'Evap ST / PB', 'Executive (SPP, SGA)', 'FP HVAC Molding L1', 'FP HVAC Molding L2', 'FP HVAC Molding L4 / L5', 'FP HVAC Molding L6', 'Facilities(IPP)', 'Facility (APP)', 'Facility (GPP)', 'Facility (SPP)', 'Final Assembling (CPS)', 'Final Assembly Inspection IPP', 'Final Inspection (APP)', 'Final Inspection (SPP)', 'Final Inspection APP - GPP', 'Frame', 'Fuel Sender', 'GIC Back Process', 'GIC Front Process', 'GIC I/F Tube Mill & Plasma Flux', 'GIC Nbf Furnace', 'GSR Core', 'GSR Crimping', 'GSR Flux Furnace', 'GSR Tube Mill ', 'General Administration APP', 'General Administration GPP', 'General Administration IPP', 'General Administration SPP', 'HR Non-Union (SPP)', 'HR Planning', 'HR Union (APP)', 'HUD', 'HVAC L1', 'HVAC L2', 'HVAC L3', 'HVAC L4', 'HVAC L5', 'HVAC L6', 'HVAC Molding L2', 'HVAC Molding L3', 'Human Resources(IPP)', 'I-VCT Valve', 'Import & Export (APP/GPP Common)', 'Import & Export (M&L)', 'Import & Export (Misc)', 'Import & Export (Motor Passthrough)', 'Information Technologies', 'Information Technologies (IPP)', 'Information Technologies (SPP)', 'Intercooler', 'JR (SPP)', 'JR Crew (IPP)', 'Jr Crew (CPS)', 'Jr Crew (EGC, MTS, APP)', 'Jr Crew (GPP)', 'LDR Back Process', 'LDR Front Process', 'LDR NBF Furnace', 'LDR Tube Mill', 'LII & LIII ISCV', 'Laboratory (SPP)', 'Logistics (CPS)', 'Logistics (Common)', 'Logistics (EC)', 'Logistics (EGC, MTS)', 'Logistics (GPP)', 'Logistics (M&L)', 'Logistics (SPP, WH Expansion)', 'Logistics (Thermal)', 'Logistics Components (EC)', 'Logistics Components (Thermal)', 'Logistics Planning Control', 'Logistics(IPP)', 'MCV', 'MCV Parts Preparation', 'MX Monozukuri Planning Common', 'Machine Common', 'Machinery & Tools', 'Machining Maintenance (EGC, MTS, APP)', 'Maintenance (EC)', 'Maintenance (Thermal)', 'Maintenance Control', 'Maintenance(IPP)', 'Manufacturing Executive', 'Manufacturing Planning', 'Manufacturing Planning (SPP)', 'Manufacturing Projects Coordination', 'Measurements (GPP)', 'Molding (CPS)', 'Molding Maintenance (GPP)', 'Molds Maintenance (CPS)', 'Molds Maintenance (Common)', 'NCCV', 'NCS Assy', 'NCS Molding', 'NDVSV (GM/Nikkei)', 'OCV Assy', 'OCV Assy (Transfer)', 'OCV Machining CR-V', 'OCV Sleeve Incl. Die Cast', 'OCV Transfer Parts', 'OE Sales', 'PC (CPS)', 'PC (EC)', 'PC (EGC, MTS) Common', 'PC (GPP)', 'PC (M&L)', 'PC (Motor Passthrough)', 'PC (Thermal)', 'PC Management', 'PCB Assembling', 'PCB SMD', 'PE (EC)', 'PE (IPP)', 'PE FA  (ME)', 'PE FA (Thermal)', 'PE Molding (ME)', 'PE Painting (ME)', 'PE Printing (ME)', 'PE Program Manager (ME)', 'PE SMD (ME)', 'PE Valve Body (EGC, MTS)', 'PE Valves (EGC, MTS)', 'PE_Executive', 'PQ ME Direct', 'PQ MTS/EGC Direct', 'PQ MTS/EGC Indirect', 'Painting & Laser Etching', 'Parts Manufacturing Center', 'Parts Quality (EC)', 'Parts Quality (Thermal)', 'Plant Management', 'Plant Staff/SPT', 'Pre-Processing (M&L)', 'Printing', 'Procurement (SPP)', 'Production (CPS)', 'Production (SPP)', 'Production Control(IPP)', 'Production Eng (GPP)', 'Production Engineering (AC ECU SMD)', 'Production General', 'Production General(IPP)', 'Productivity', 'Productivity (CPS)', 'Productivity (EGC, MTS)', 'Productivity (GPP)', 'Purchasing', 'Purchasing MRO', 'Purchasing Planning', 'QA (EGC, MTS, GPP)', 'QC (EGC, MTS, GPP)', 'QE Executive', 'QE Planning', 'Quality Assurance', 'Quality Assurance(IPP)', 'Quality Control (CPS)', 'Quality Control (EC)', 'Quality Control (EGC, MTS)', 'Quality Control (Thermal)', 'Quality Control Systems', 'SCM Management', 'SCM PDE', 'SCM PE', 'SCM PQ', 'SCM SDA', 'SHE (GPP)', 'SHE (IPP)', 'SHE (SPP)', 'SHE MX Region', 'Safety (APP, GPP)', 'Skill Olympics', 'Slant Connector', 'Sound Line', 'Special Team (SPP)', 'Stator Localization', 'Sub Assy', 'TIE (SPP)', 'TIE/Industrial Eng', 'TPM', 'TPM and Maintenance Planning', 'Tool & Die Maintenance', 'Tool Control', 'Total Industrial Eng', 'Training', 'Training IPP', 'Training NED', 'VB Assembly and Inspection L1', 'VB Assembly and Inspection L2', 'VB Body Machining Measurements', 'VB Die Casting L1', 'VB Die Casting L2 Upper Die Step 1', 'VB Die Casting L3 Lower Die Step 1', 'VB Die Casting L4 Upper Die Step 2', 'VB Die Casting L5 Lower Die Step 2', 'VB Lower Machining L1', 'VB Lower Machining L2', 'VB Lower Machining L3', 'VB Solenoid Assy', 'VB Solenoid Machining L1', 'VB Solenoid Machining L2', 'VB Solenoid Machining L3', 'VB Solenoid Machining Measurements', 'VB Upper Machining L1', 'VB Upper Machining L2', 'VB Upper Machining L3', 'VB Washing L1', 'VB Washing L2', 'VCT Assy', 'VCT Machining Aluminium', 'VCT Measurements', 'VCT Sintering', 'VSV, D-VSV, CCV', 'WSS Assy', 'Water Pump/Reserve Tank']
    },
    {question:"Dep. Class",
    answers:['Common', 'Exclusive']},
    {question:'Position Name',
    answers:['3Indirect Material', '3Production', '4New Products', '4PE Manufacturing', '4Plant Staff', '4Production', '4Production Planning', '4Productivity', '4QA operation', '4Special Team', '5Direct Material', '5Indirect Material', '5New Products', '5Process Engineering', '6Design', '6Plant Staff', '6Production', 'ASISTENTE', 'Accounts payable', 'Administration', 'Administration & Spare parts', 'Analista', 'Business Planning', 'C MEJORA', 'C Mejora', 'Continuous Improvement', 'Cost Accounting', 'Cost Planning', 'Customer contact', 'Design', 'Direct Material', 'Director', 'ENTRENAMIENTO B1', 'ENTRENAMIENTO C', 'Entrenamiento B1', 'Environment', 'Especialista', 'Especialista AVANZADO', 'Expats', 'Facilities', 'General Accounting', 'General Manager', 'HR', 'HR Generalist', 'HR and GA', 'IS Support', 'ISO TS & Audits', 'Import & Export', 'Indirect Material', 'Industrial Engineering', 'JEFE DE GRUPO', 'JEFE DE GRUPO AVANZADO', 'Laboratory', 'Legal Compliance', 'M&T', 'M&T Design', 'M&T Planning / Fabrication', 'Machines & Molding', 'Maintenance', 'Material Planning', 'Measurements', 'New Products', 'OPERADOR EXPERTO', 'Operador', 'Operador Avanzado', 'Operador Experto', 'Operador Junior', 'PE Manufacturing', 'PRACTICANTE', 'Parts Quality', 'Plant Engineering', 'Plant Staff', 'Practicante', 'Process Engineering', 'Procurement', 'Production', 'Production Control', 'Production Planning', 'Productivity', 'QA operation', 'QC operation', 'Quality Assurance', 'Quality Control', 'SUPERVISOR', 'Safety', 'Sales', 'Special Team', 'Subgerente', 'Systems Development', 'Tax', 'Tool & Die', 'Trainee A', 'Translator', 'Troubleshooting', 'VP', 'Warehouse']},
    {question:'Position ID',
    answers:['0 - Entrenamiento A', '1 - Entrenamiento B1', '10 - Especialista Avanzado', '10 - Jefe De Grupo Avanzado', '10 - Tecnico Experto', '11 - Supervisor', '12 - Subgerente', '13 - Gerente', '14 - Gerente General', '15 - Director', '16 - Vicepresidente', '2 - C Mejora', '3 - Entrenamiento C', '4 - Operador Junior', '5 - Operador', '6 - Operador Avanzado', '6 - Practicante', '7 - Asistente', '7 - Operador Experto', '7 - Tecnico Junior', '8 - Analista', '8 - Sublider', '8 - Tecnico', '9 - Especialista', '9 - Jefe De Grupo', '9 - Tecnico Avanzado', '9 - Traductor']},
    {question:'Employee Type',
    answers:['Empleado', 'Expatriados', 'Practicante', 'Sindicalizado', 'Traductor']
    },
    {question:'Nacionality',
    answers:['Japon√©s', 'Mexicano']},
    {question:'Status',
    answers:['Active', 'Quit', 'Terminated']},
    {question:'Turn Code',
    answers:['14281', '14282', '14283', '340001', '4158', '4159', '4160', '4161', '4162', '4163', '4165', '4166', 'OFICINA SIND. DE 08:00 A 17:36']},
    {question:['Gender'],
    answers:['Female', 'Male']},
    {question:'Plant',
    answers:['APP', 'GPP', 'IPP', 'SPP']},
    {question:'Type',
    answers:['Direct', 'Indirect', 'SGA']},
    {question:'Category',
    answers:['DNMX | APP/GPP Manufacturing', 'DNMX | APP/GPP PC-Logistics', 'DNMX | APP/GPP PE', 'DNMX | APP/GPP Purchasing', 'DNMX | APP/GPP QE', 'DNMX | BP-Acc', 'DNMX | Corporate Executive', 'DNMX | HR-IT-FAC-GA', 'DNMX | Irapuato', 'DNMX | M&T', 'DNMX | Monozukuri center', 'DNMX | PE Parts', 'DNMX | SCM', 'DNMX | SPP Administration/Manufacturing', 'DNMX | SPP Plant function', 'DNMX | Sales']},
    {question:'Function',
    answers:['APP-GPP SHE/TPM Planning', 'APP2', 'Assy Maintenance GPP', 'BP / Acc', 'Bajio Admin', 'Continuous Improvement', 'EC Eng/Prod', 'ELEF Eng', 'Exe & Other', 'Facilities', 'GPP', 'HR Non Union/IT (All Plants)', 'HR Union / AS (All plants)', 'IPP', 'M&T', 'M&T / Die', 'Maintenance CPS/Die', 'Maintenance EGC, MTS', 'Molding Maintenance GPP', 'Monozukuri Planning', 'Other Not used', 'PC Bajio', 'PC Operation', 'PE ECU', 'PE ME', 'PE MTS Assy', 'PE Parts Eng', 'PE Planning', 'PMC', 'PR CPS', 'PR Plant Staff', 'Planning', 'Planning PC', 'Plant Mfg Planning', 'Purchasing', 'QE', 'QE CPS', 'QE MTS', 'QE Planning', 'QE SPP', 'SCM', 'SHE Planning (Region)', 'SPP Common', 'Sales', 'TAC PDE', 'TAC Production', 'TH Eng']},
    {question:'Area',
    answers:[' PR CPS3 Final Assy PCB-SMD', 'APP-GPP Maint-T/D-Die Cast', 'APP-GPP SHE', 'Accounting', 'After Market', 'Asocc. Service', 'BP', 'Design', 'Die Shop', 'Executives', 'Ext & Gral Affairs\n/Legal', 'Facilities APP/GPP', 'Facilities IPP', 'Facilities SPP', 'HR Non-Union', 'HR Union', 'I/E', 'IPP', 'IPP Maintenance', 'IPP PE', 'IPP Production', 'IPP QA', 'IT', 'Import/Export', 'Labo / PQ', 'Logistics & WH Planning', 'M&T SPP', 'Machinery', 'Maintenance APP Plant1', 'Maintenance APP2', 'Maintenance Common', 'Maintenance GPP', 'Maintenance SPP', 'Manufacturing GPP', 'Mfg Planning-IOT', 'Monozukuri Planning', 'Other Not used', 'PC CPS', 'PC MTC Prod. Planning', 'PC Planning', 'PC1: Thermal', 'PC2: ELEFI', 'PE ECU', 'PE ELEF', 'PE ME', 'PE MTS', 'PE Parts Eng', 'PE Planning', 'PE Thermal', 'PMC', 'PQ APP', 'PR CPS1 Parts-Print/ Mold/ Paint', 'PR CPS2 Final Assy', 'PR. EC', 'PR. GIC/LDR', 'PR. GSR/EVA', 'PR. HVAC/ECM Assy', 'PR. M&L', 'PR. MTS AT/OCV', 'PR. MTS GPP', 'PR. MTS MCV', 'PR. MTS VB 1', 'PR. MTS VCT/WSS', 'PR. TAC Mold', 'Plant Support', 'Purchashing', 'Purchashing MRO', 'Purchasing Eng', 'QE APP - GPP', 'QE APP1', 'QE APP2', 'QE GPP', 'QE Planning', 'QE SPP', 'QE1: Thermal', 'SCM', 'SHE Planning', 'SHE-HR-IT-ACC-PUR', 'Sales Office', 'TIE', 'Tool Control', 'WH (SPP & IPP)', 'Warehouse (APP/GPP)']},
    {question:'Business Unit',
    answers:['Asmo', 'Body Motor', 'CPS', 'Common', 'EC', 'ECU', 'EGC', 'EGC, MTS', 'M&T', 'ME', 'MTS', 'MTS,EGC', 'Sensing', 'Sound', 'Thermal', 'Wiper & Washer']},
    {question:'Manager',
    answers:['Alejandro Mendoza', 'Alejandro Vargas', 'Ana Mar√≠a Garc√≠a', 'Andr√©s Morales', 'Andr√©s Ram√≠rez', 'Antonio Gonz√°lez', 'Arturo Gonz√°lez', 'Arturo L√≥pez', 'Arturo Morales', 'Arturo P√©rez', 'Brenda Hern√°ndez', 'Carlos Alberto Ruiz', 'Carlos Alberto Soto', 'Carlos Alberto Torres', 'Carlos Antonio Ruiz', 'Carlos Hern√°ndez', 'Carlos Hinojosa', 'Daniel Foster', 'Daniel Morales', 'Daniel Soto', 'Daniel S√°nchez', 'Eduardo Morales', 'Eduardo Ram√≠rez', 'Eduardo Soto', 'Eduardo S√°nchez', 'Fernando S√°nchez', 'Fernando Torres', 'Francisco Javier P√©rez', 'Francisco Javier Torres', 'Francisco Jim√©nez', 'Francisco Ram√≠rez', 'Guillermo P√©rez', 'Guillermo S√°nchez', 'Guillermo Torres', 'Hiroshi Nakamura', 'Hiroshi Tanaka', 'Hiroshi Yamamoto', 'Jorge Luis Soto', 'Jorge Mart√≠nez', 'Jos√© Antonio Ram√≠rez', 'Jos√© Luis Rodr√≠guez', 'Jos√© Luis S√°nchez', 'Juan Carlos Ruiz', 'Juan Carlos Soto', 'Juan Carlos Torres', 'Juan Pablo Torres', 'Karina Torres', 'Kazuki Nakamura', 'Kazuki Tanaka', 'Kenji Nakamura', 'Kenji Suzuki', 'Laura Gonz√°lez', 'Laura P√©rez', 'Laura Rodr√≠guez', 'Luis Alberto P√©rez', 'Luis Alberto Torres', 'Luis Eduardo Soto', 'Luis Morales', 'Mart√≠n Gonz√°lez', 'Mar√≠a Fern√°ndez', 'Miguel √Ångel Ram√≠rez', 'Miguel √Ångel S√°nchez', 'Miguel √Ångel Torres', 'No√© P√©rez', 'Patricia Soto', 'Pedro Morales', 'Pedro Ram√≠rez', 'Ra√∫l Gonz√°lez', 'Ra√∫l Medina', 'Ricardo P√©rez', 'Ricardo Soto', 'Rodrigo Torres', 'Satoshi Suzuki', 'Takashi Nakamura', 'Takashi Suzuki', 'Yuki Tanaka']},
    {question:'GM',
    answers:['Alejandro Mendoza', 'Alejandro Vargas', 'Andr√©s Ram√≠rez', 'Andr√©s Torres', 'Brenda P√©rez', 'Carlos Alberto Ruiz', 'Carlos Antonio Ruiz', 'Carlos Hern√°ndez', 'Eduardo Soto', 'Eduardo S√°nchez', 'Fernando S√°nchez', 'Francisco Javier Torres', 'Francisco Jim√©nez', 'Francisco Ram√≠rez', 'Guillermo S√°nchez', 'Hiroshi Nakamura', 'Hiroshi Tanaka', 'Hiroshi Yamamoto', 'Jos√© Luis Rodr√≠guez', 'Kazuki Tanaka', 'Kenji Nakamura', 'Kenji Suzuki', 'Laura Gonz√°lez', 'Luis Eduardo Soto', 'Miguel √Ångel Ram√≠rez', 'Miguel √Ångel S√°nchez', 'Miguel √Ångel Torres', 'No√© P√©rez', 'Pedro S√°nchez', 'Ricardo P√©rez', 'Ricardo Soto', 'Rodrigo Torres', 'Satoshi Yamamoto', 'Takashi Nakamura', 'Takashi Suzuki', 'Yuki Tanaka']},
    {question:'Director',
    answers:['Alejandro Mendoza', 'Andr√©s Torres', 'Carlos Alberto S√°nchez', 'Carlos Hern√°ndez', 'Eduardo Soto', 'Eduardo S√°nchez', 'Guillermo S√°nchez', 'Hiroshi Nakamura', 'Hiroshi Tanaka', 'Kazuki Nakamura', 'Kenji Nakamura', 'Miguel √Ångel Torres', 'No√© P√©rez', 'Ra√∫l Medina', 'Ricardo P√©rez', 'Rodrigo Torres', 'Takashi Suzuki', 'Takuya Suzuki']},
    {question:'VP',
    answers:['Alejandro Mendoza', 'Hiroshi Nakamura', 'Kenji Nakamura', 'No√© P√©rez', 'Ra√∫l Medina', 'Takuya Suzuki']},
    {question:'BP',
    answers:['Hiroshi Tanaka', 'Kazuki Suzuki', 'Kenji Nakamura', 'Laura Gonz√°lez', 'Satoshi Suzuki', 'Yuki Tanaka']},

]